[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many people signed the US Declaration of Independence on July 4,1776?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["55", "0", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of the following are treatments for rheumatoid arthritis EXCEPT which one?", "correct_answer": "Carbamazepine", "incorrect_answers": ["Hydroxychloroquine", "Gold", "Prednisone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Disney film is this dialogue from:\nUh-oh.\nDont tell me. Were about to go over a huge waterfall.\nYep.\nSharp rocks at the bottom?\nMost likely.\nBring it on?", "correct_answer": "The Emperors New Groove", "incorrect_answers": ["Mulan", "A Goofy Movie", "The Brave Little Toaster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which of these films did Mel Brooks win an Academy Award?", "correct_answer": "The Producers", "incorrect_answers": ["Blazing Saddles", "High Anxiety", "Silent Movie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of these Al Pacino movies were released in the 1970s. Which one was not?", "correct_answer": "Scarface", "incorrect_answers": ["The Godfather: Part II", "The Godfather", "Serpico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Buildings can explode due to low pressure that comes with tornadoes.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Bond movie, Thunderball, the villains yacht, called this, had a crucial part in S.P.E.C.T.R.E.s evil scheme.", "correct_answer": "Disco Volante", "incorrect_answers": ["Terrible Triton", "Ocean Pirate", "Merry Mermaid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Drew Barrymores godfather?", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Alfred Hitchcock", "Robert De Niro", "Marlon Brando"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the creator of the first steam locomotive?", "correct_answer": "Richard Trevithick", "incorrect_answers": ["Ronald Von Heldenberger", "Robert Fulton", "Robert Watts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was on the cover of the first issue of  People magazine?", "correct_answer": "Mia Farrow", "incorrect_answers": ["Elvis Presley", "Joseph G. Cannon", "Lucille Ball"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many major planets are there in the Solar System?", "correct_answer": "8", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "9", "11"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of nuts is used for the preparation of the traditional Spanish pie Tarta de Santiago?", "correct_answer": "Almonds", "incorrect_answers": ["Walnuts", "Pistachio nuts", "Peanuts"]}]